Guide to the Poetry: A Magazine of Verse Records 1895-1961
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Administrative Files, 1954-1961
  - Subseries 1: Contributors -- Manuscripts and Correspondence
    - O'Doherty, Brian SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Oe-Og, Oerke, Andrew Ogburn, [?] Ogilvie, John T. (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - O'Gorman, Ned SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - O'Gorman, Ned SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - O'Gorman, Ned SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - O'Gorman, Ned (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - O'Gorman, Ned (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - O'Gorman, Ned (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - O'Gorman, Pat (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - O'Hara, Frank SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - O'Hara, Frank SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - O'Hara, Frank (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Ol, Olaguer, Valdemar Oleshak, Theodore Oleson, Helmer O. (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Olson, Elder SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Olson, Elder SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Ol-O’N, Olson, Neil Bradford O'Mara, Jerome L. O'More, Haven O'Neill, John (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Oppen, George SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Or, Oras, Ants Orel, Harold Orente, Rose Orgel, Stephen Orlinsky, David E. (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Orlovitz, Gil (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - Orlovitz, Gil (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Orr, Anne (Box 130, Folder 25)
    - Ostroff, Anthony (Box 130, Folder 26)
    - Ostroff, Anthony (Box 130, Folder 27)
    - Os-Ow, O'Sullivan, Seumus Outram, Richard Overdick, Patricia Owen, Guy Owens, Ethel Werfel Owens, Rochelle (Box 130, Folder 28)
    - Oxenhandler, Neal (Box 130, Folder 29)
    - Pa, Pace, William F. Pacifici, Sergio J. (Box 130, Folder 30)
    - Pack, Robert M. (Box 130, Folder 31)
    - Pa, Packard, William Page, Alan Page, P. K. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Pa SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Paglir, Joseph M. Palchi, Alfredo de Paley, Morton D. Pallister, Jan Palmer, Edgar Palmer, Phyllis M. Palombo, Stanley Paolucci, Anne Paquette, Donald J. Parkinson, Thomas Parleinson, Thomas (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Pa, Parks, Lloyd C. Partelleau, Marlon Paston, Linda (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Patchen, Kenneth (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Patchen, Kenneth SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Patchen, Kenneth SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Pa-Pe, Pate, James Meredith Pati, Gourchandra Patterson, David A. Paul, David Pausch, Emily Pavlakis, James Payton, Robert Kent Pedrick, Jean Pekin, Meriam (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Pe, Peachy, Frederic SEE ALSO OVERSIZE Pearson, Norman Holmes (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Pe, Peña, Horacio Pennell, Joseph Stanley Perdichij George Perkins, David Perlberg, Mark M. Perlongo, Robert A. (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Pe SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Perreau-Saussine, Richard Perret, Christopher (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Perry, Ronald SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Perry, Ronald SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Perry, Ronald (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Perry, Ronald (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Perse, St. John (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Perse, St. John (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Pe, Peter, John Petersen, Donald (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Petrie, Paul SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Petrie, Paul (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Pe-Pf, Pettinella, Dora M. Pettitt, Kenneth Peyre, Henri M. Pfeiffer, Eric (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - Ph, Phelps, Lyon Phelps Mary Phillips, Katherine Phillips, Larry C. Phillips, Mrs. McGrigor Phillips, William Pick, John Pickard, Cynthia Pike, Judith J. (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Pillin, William SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Pissarro, Ruth (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Pitchford, Kenneth (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Planz, Allen (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - Plath, Sylvia SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 131, Folder 26)
    - Plath, Sylvia (Box 131, Folder 27)
    - Plumb, Ogden (Box 131, Folder 28)
    - Plutzik, Hyam (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Po, Poda, Louis Poemeroy, Marnie Poggioli, Renato Poindexter, Joseph Polk, Emily (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Pomeroy, Ralph SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Pomeroy, Ralph SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Pomeroy, Ralph (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Pomeroy, Ralph (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Ponsot, Marie SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Ponsot, Marie (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Ponsot, Marie (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Porter, Fairfield (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Posner, David L. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Po, Postell, Thomas Poster, William S. Pound, Ezra (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Po-Py, Powell, Clarence Alva Powell, Marcus Paul Powell, Peter Powers, Jessica Pratt, Arthur Pratt, David Pratt, William C. Preston, William Prettyman, Alfred E. Prigogine, Hélène Pritchard, Errol Pritchard, Sheila Probyn, Hugh Prouty, Morton D. Provost, Carl K. Purcell, Hugh Dominic Purnell, Idella Pym, John (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Q-Ra, Quinn, J. R. Rafat, Taufiq (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Rago, Henry (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Rago, Henry (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Raine, Kathleen SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Rainer, Dachine (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Raiziss, Sonia SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - Raiziss, Sonia SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 20)
    - Raiziss, Sonia SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 21)
    - Ra, Rajan, B. Raju, C. Raju, P. T. Rakowski, Leonard Ramanujan, A. K. (Box 132, Folder 22)
    - Ra, Randall, Belle Randall, Huberta Frets Randall, Julia Randolph, John George Rane, Ed Rangachari, M.V.V.K. (Box 132, Folder 23)
    - Ransom, John Crowe (Box 132, Folder 24)
    - Ra, Rao, K. Raghavendria Rapp, Rosemary Ráshed, N. M. (Box 132, Folder 25)
    - Ra, Rattray, David Rawley, Sue Rawlins, Winifred Ray, David Ray, Lila (Box 132, Folder 26)
    - Ra, Rayaprol, Srinivas Rayford, Julian Lee Raymond, Richard C. Raynor, Owen (Box 132, Folder 27)
    - Read, Herbert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 132, Folder 28)
    - Reaney, James (Box 132, Folder 29)
    - Re, Reaney, Eilis Reavey, George Reber, Patricia Murphy Rechtien, John Reck, Michael Redding, William J. (Box 132, Folder 30)
    - Redgrove, Peter (Box 132, Folder 31)
    - Re, Reed, John F. Rees, Ennis Reeve, F. D. Rehder, R. M. (Box 132, Folder 32)
    - Reid, Alastair (Box 132, Folder 33)
    - Re, Reising, Otto Rella, Ettore Remus, Stanley, J. Replansky, Naomi Requé, Bill (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Reynolds, Charles (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Reynolds, Tim (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Re-Ri SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Reznikoff, Charles Rice, Jaw W. Rich, Adrienne Rich, Bertha (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Richards, I. A. (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Ri, Richards, Mary Caroline Richardson, Dorothy Lee Richer, Paul Rickel, William Riddee, Alan J. Ridland, John M. (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Ridler, Anne SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Rivera, William (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Rizzardi, Alfredo (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Ro, Roach, Helen Robbins, Martin Roberts, Dorothy Roberts, Lynette Robin, Ralph Robins, Rae Rocha, [?] (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Roche, Paul (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Rodger, Ian G. (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Roditi, Edouard (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Roditi, Edouard (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Roditi, Edouard (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Rodman, Selden (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Roethke, Theodore (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Roethke, Theodore (Box 133, Folder 20)
    - Ro, Rogers, Daniel J. Rogers, Howard Emerson Rogers, Preston Ragowsky, Nicholas Rukeah, David Romney, Barbara Rosekrans, Sarah D. (Box 133, Folder 21)
    - Roseliep, Raymond (Box 133, Folder 22)
    - Ro, Rosen, Stanley Rosenberg, James L. Rosenberger, Coleman Rosenburg, Robert K. Rosenfeld, Isaac Roseveare, Edith (Box 133, Folder 23)
    - Rosenthal, M. L. (Box 133, Folder 24)
    - Roskolenko, Harry (Box 133, Folder 25)
    - Roskolenko, Harry (Box 133, Folder 26)
    - Ro, Ross, Lawrence Rosso, Jean-Claude (Box 133, Folder 27)
    - Rosten, Norman (Box 133, Folder 28)
    - Ro-Ru, Rothenberg, Jerome Rountzounis Roy, K. Rubenstein, Richard Rubin, David Lee (Box 133, Folder 29)
    - Rubin, Larry (Box 133, Folder 30)
    - Ru, Ruderman, Oscar Rudnik, Raphael Ruhen, Olaf (Box 133, Folder 31)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel (Box 133, Folder 32)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel (Box 133, Folder 33)
    - Russell, Paula (Box 133, Folder 34)
    - Russell, Peter (Box 133, Folder 35)
    - Ru-Ry, Russell, Sydney King Rutkowski, B. Richard Rutsale, Vern Ryan, James J. Ryan, Michael Ryan, Pat (Box 133, Folder 36)
    - Sa, Sachs, David Sack, Paula Sadashiv, Rawoot Safferson, Muriel Sahley, Billie J. St. Martin, Hardie Sakal, Albert Salazar, Gerard M. Salim-ur-rahman, M. (Box 133, Folder 37)
    - Salinger, Herman SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 133, Folder 38)
    - Salinger, Herman (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Salisbury, Ralph J. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Salomon, I. L. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Sa, Samperi, Frank Samson, Barbara L. (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Sandburg, Carl (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Sandburg, Helga (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Sandeen, Ernest SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Sandeen, Ernest SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Sandeen, Ernest (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Sa, Sander, David M. Sanders, Gerald Sandy, Stephen Sanel, Mary Beale Sangu, Makolo Santos, Bienvenido N. Sarabhai, Bharati Sarley, Virginia M. (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Saroyan, William (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Sarton, May SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Sato, Satoru, correspondence (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Sato, Satoru, Japanese issue (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Sato, Satoru, Japanese issue (Box 134, Folder 15)
    - Sato, Satoru, Japanese issue (Box 134, Folder 16)
    - Sato, Satoru, Japanese issue (Box 134, Folder 17)
    - Sato, Satoru, Japanese issue (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - Sato, Satoru, Japanese issue (Box 134, Folder 19)
    - Sato, Satoru, Japanese issue (Box 134, Folder 20)
    - Sato, Satoru, Japanese issue (Box 134, Folder 21)
    - Sa-Sc, Saunders, Josephine Saunders, William Savory, Ted Saxon, A. H. Sayers, Michael Saynet, S. M. Scannell, Bernon Scarbrough, George (Box 134, Folder 22)
    - Sc, Scarfe, Frances Schall, Sidore Schaumann, Herbert Schaumburger (Box 134, Folder 23)
    - Schevill, James (Box 134, Folder 24)
    - Sc, Schmidt, Dorothea Schmidt, Judith Schmitz, Lennis Schmucker, Walter Schneider, Mrs. Herman Schneider, Renée E. Schott, Hal Schroeter, James Schumann, Art Schupf, Lucienne Schuyler, James (Box 134, Folder 25)
    - Schwartz, Delmore SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 134, Folder 26)
    - Schwartz, Delmore (Box 134, Folder 27)
    - Schwartz, Irwin (Box 134, Folder 28)
    - Schwartz, Selwyn (Box 134, Folder 29)
    - Sc, Schwebell, Gertrude Clorius Schweppenbauser, Marietta V. Sconffes, Roberta Scott, Peter Dale (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Scott, Tom SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Scott, Tom (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Tom (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Scott, Tom (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Scott, Winfield Townley SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Scott, Winfield Townley (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Sc, Scotton, Carol Myers Scribner, Charles (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Scully, James (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Se, Sebba, Gregor Seidel, Frederick Seif, Morton Seifer, Mark Seiger, Marvin L. Seitlin, Percy Seljouk, M. A. (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Sellin, Eric (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Se, Selman, Jerry Serrano, Miguel Sethi, Narendra K. (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Sexton, Anne SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Sh, Shah, Romesh Shapiro, David (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Shapiro, Karl, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Shapiro, Karl, manuscripts SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Shapiro, Karl, manuscripts (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Shapiro, Karl, correspondence (Box 135, Folder 18)
    - Shapiro, Karl, correspondence (Box 135, Folder 19)
    - Shapiro, Karl, correspondence (Box 135, Folder 20)
    - Shapiro, Karl, correspondence (Box 135, Folder 21)
    - Shapiro, Karl, correspondence (Box 135, Folder 22)
    - Shapiro, Karl, correspondence (Box 135, Folder 23)
    - Sh, Shapiro, Norman Sharrock, Roger Sharuma, Mausa Ram Shaw, Louis Agassiz Shelley, Robert Shelton, Ernestyne Shenk, Cyrus E. Shepard, Alta Sherman, Jory Sherrard, Elizabeth M. Sherrerd, Henry D. M. Sherwin, Judith Johnson (Box 135, Folder 24)
    - Sh-Si, Shiffert, Edith M. Shinner, E. G. Shonbrun, Margaret Shore, Winnifred Shove, Fredegond Shridharoni, Krishnalal Shulenberger, Arvid Siegel, Eli Silk, Dennis (Box 135, Folder 25)
    - Silkin, Jon (Box 135, Folder 26)
    - Si, Silver, Harold Simmons, Charles Simmons, James Simon, John Simpson, Louis Simpson, Peter L. Simpson, R. A. Sinclair, Keith (Box 135, Folder 27)
    - Singer, Helen SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 135, Folder 28)
    - Si, Singer, Leslie Singh, Harbans (Box 135, Folder 29)
    - Sitwell, Edith SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 135, Folder 30)
    - Sitwell, Edith (Box 135, Folder 31)
    - Sk-Sm, Skillin, Glenn B. Skinner, Knute Slater, Stanley Laurence Slavutych, Yar Sloan, Jacob Sloan, Jocelyn Macy Sloanaker, Hiram Lyday Slonim, Ruth Smail, Annette K. Smart, Susan (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Sm, Smith, A. J. M. Smith, Franc Smith Francis W. Smith, Iain Chrichton (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Sm, Smith Jerry Smith, John Smith, Ray Smith, Rex (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Sydney Goodsir SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Weire (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Smith, William Jay SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Smith, William Jay SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Smith, William Jay (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Sm-Sn, Smithyman, Kendrick Snidere, Velta (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Snodgrass, W. D. (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Snyder, Franklyn B. (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Sobiloff, Hy (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Soles, Fiary (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Solomon, Marvin (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Solomon, Marvin SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Solomon, Marvin (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - So, Som, Sovon Somerville, Colin Sontag, Ray Sorell, Walter (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - Souster, Raymond (Box 136, Folder 18)
    - So-Sp, Southam, Brian Southard, W. P. Southworth, Sharon Spacks, Barry Spark, Muriel Sparks, Merrill Sparshott, Francis Spateholts, Richard (Box 136, Folder 19)
    - Spender, Stephen (Box 136, Folder 20)
    - Sp, Spicer, Jack Spielberg, Peter Spingarn, Lawrence P. (Box 136, Folder 21)
    - Squires, Radcliffe SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 136, Folder 22)
    - Stafford, William SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 136, Folder 23)
    - Stafford, William SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 136, Folder 24)
    - Stafford, William SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 136, Folder 25)
    - Stafford, William (Box 136, Folder 26)
    - Stafford, William (Box 136, Folder 27)
    - Stallman, R. W. (Box 136, Folder 28)
    - Stanford, Ann (Box 136, Folder 29)
    - Stanford, Don (Box 136, Folder 30)
    - Stange, G. Robert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - St, Stanley, George Stanley, Leon Stanley, Louis Stapleton, Laurence (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Starbuck, George (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Starbuck, Janice (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - St, Stead, C. K. Steen, James T. (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Stefanile, Felix SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Stefanile, Felix (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Stegner, Wallace (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - St, Stein, Elliott Stein, Gisela Stein, M. R. (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Steiner, Stan (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - St, Steinman, D. B. Steinmetz, Barbara Stella, Sister Maris Stephens, William Stern, Gerd (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Stern, Richard (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Stepanchev, Stephen (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Stepanchev, Stephen (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - St, Stephan, Ruth Sterling, Ann (Box 137, Folder 15)
    - Stevens, Wallace SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 137, Folder 16)
    - Stevenston, Ellen (Box 137, Folder 17)
    - Stewart, Desmond SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 137, Folder 18)
    - St, Stewart, Dolores Stiehl, Harry Stock, C. Wharton Stock, Noel (Box 137, Folder 19)
    - Stock, Robert SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 137, Folder 20)
    - Stock, Robert (Box 137, Folder 21)
    - St, Stockton, Adrian Stoloff, Carolyn (Box 137, Folder 22)
    - Stone, Ruth (Box 137, Folder 23)
    - Stone, Ruth (Box 137, Folder 24)
    - St, Stone, Walter Story, Christopher Stoutenburg, Adrien Strand, Mark Stresino, Edw. (Box 137, Folder 25)
    - Strickhausen, Harry SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 137, Folder 26)
    - Strickhausen, Harry (Box 137, Folder 27)
    - St-Su, Stryck, Lucien Stuart, Evelyn Marie Stuuman, Edith Sullivan, Nancy Sullivan, Philip (Box 137, Folder 28)
    - Su-Sw, Summers, Hollis Sussman, Robert Sutherland, John Svaglic, Martin Swallow, Alan Swan, Emma Swan, Jon (Box 137, Folder 29)
    - Sward, Robert S. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 137, Folder 30)
    - Sward, Robert S. (Box 137, Folder 31)
    - Sward, Robert S. (Box 137, Folder 32)
    - Sw SEE ALSO OVERSIZE, Sweeney, John L. Sweeney, Seán Sweney, Wilfred O. (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Swenson, May SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Swenson, May (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Sw-Ta, Swift, Joan Angevine Swiggett, Glen Levin Sylvester, William Tadokoro, Nobushige (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Tagliabue, John SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Tagliabue, John (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Tagliabue, John (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Tambimuttu, Thurimhurairajah (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Tambimuttu, Thurimhurairajah (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Tambimuttu, Thurimhurairajah (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Tambimuttu, Thurimhurairajah (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Ta, Tamkus, Daniel Tangherlini, Frank R. (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Tate, Allen (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Ta-Th, Taub, Betty E. Taylor, Eleanor Ross Taylor, Harry W. Taylor, K. P. A. Tëach, Gary Teljair, Havey Templin, E. H. Terrell, P. F. Thanes, Martha Banning Thapar, Romila Tharp, Roland Thieme, Theodore (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, Caitlin (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Th, Thomas, Calvin, Jr. Thomas, Catherine (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, Dylan SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - Th, Thomas, Joan Thomas, Marilyn Thomas, Rosemary Thomas, Stephen Thomason, Edwin Thompson, George (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Thompson, John SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 19)
    - Thompson, John (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Th-Ti, Thompson, Juliet Thompson, Patsy Thompson, Paul D. Thorpe, Peter Tiemann, Georganne (Box 138, Folder 21)
    - Tiempo, Edith SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 22)
    - Ti, Tillinghast, Richard Tinkham, Charles B. (Box 138, Folder 23)
    - Todd, Ruthven SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 24)
    - To, Tolson, M. B. Tomaso, Richard G. (Box 138, Folder 25)
    - Tomlinson, Charles SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 26)
    - Tomlinson, Charles SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 27)
    - Tomlinson, Charles SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 28)
    - Tomlinson, Charles SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 138, Folder 29)
    - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 138, Folder 30)
    - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - To, Tompkins, Nancy Baker Tong, Raymond Tongue, Margaret Toatell, Jack Topper, W. S. Tornquist, Dagni Torres, Emanuel Touster, Saul (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - To-Tr, Townsend, Emily Trakl, Georg SEE ALSO OVERSIZE Treadgold, Donald W. (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Triem, Eve SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Tr-Tu, Troy, William Tucker, Martin Tucker, Nell Turco, Lewis Turnbull, Gael (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Turner, Alva N. (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Tu, Turner, George Turner, James Turner, Lorenzo D. Turner, Myron Turner, W. Price (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Tu-Ty, Turnoy, Betty Tyler, Marshall (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Tyler, Parker SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Tyler, Parker (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Tyler, Parker (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Tyler, Parker (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Tz-Un, Tze-chiang, Chao Ulrey, Walter Earle Unger, Leonard Unterecker, John (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Untermeyer, Jean Starr (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Updike, John (Box 139, Folder 17)
    - Urdang, Constance SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 139, Folder 18)
    - Urdang, Constance (Box 139, Folder 19)
    - Ur-Va, Urquhart, James Usher, Jerry D. Valéry, Paul Valicha, K. D. (Box 139, Folder 20)
    - Vance, Thomas SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 139, Folder 21)
    - Va, Vanderworth Van Dore, Wade (Box 139, Folder 22)
    - Van Doren, Mark (Box 139, Folder 23)
    - Van Duyn, Mona SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 139, Folder 24)
    - Van Duyn, Mona SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 139, Folder 25)
    - Van Duyn, Mona (Box 139, Folder 26)
    - Va, Van Keuren, W. G. Vaughan, Robert Vaughan, William Knowlton (Box 139, Folder 27)
    - Vazakas, Byron SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 139, Folder 28)
    - Ve-Vi, Vecchio, Gloria Calcina del Veen, Adnan van der Veeraraghavan, V. Velisaratos, Jason Velton, William Venel, Henri de Ver Becke, W. Edwin Verhaeren, Emile Verma, D. P. Victor, Florence Viereck, George Sylvester (Box 139, Folder 29)
    - Viereck, Peter (Box 139, Folder 30)
    - Viereck, Peter (Box 139, Folder 31)
    - Vi-Vr, Villa, Voré Vincent, Agnes Vincent, Howard P. Vogt, Vivian Von Scholz Vope, Givendolyn Vroman, L. (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Wagner, Geoffrey SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Wagoner, David SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Wagoner, David SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Wagoner, David (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Wain, John (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Wa, Wakeman, Frederic Wakoski, Diane SEE ALSO OVERSIZE Walker, Dorothea Walker, Faye Chilcote Walker, Mary Fraser Wallace, Robert (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Walsh, Chad (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Wa, Walsh, Peter B. Walters, W. R. (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Walton, Eda Lou SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Walton, Eda Lou (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Wa, Wang, David Rafael Wang, John C. Warburg, Sandol Ward, H. V. Warren, Austin (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Warren, Robert Penn (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Wa, Wassall, Irma Watkins, Edward Watkins, Geoffrey (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Watkins, Vernon SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - Watkins, Vernon SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - Watkins, Vernon (Box 140, Folder 17)
    - Watkins, Vernon (Box 140, Folder 18)
    - Watkins, Vernon (Box 140, Folder 19)
    - Watkins, Vernon (Box 140, Folder 20)
    - Watson, James S. (pseudonym "W. C. Blum") SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 140, Folder 21)
    - Wa-We, Watson, Robert W. Watson, R. V. Watt, William Weales, Gerald Weathers, Winston Weathersby, William Alton (Box 140, Folder 22)
    - Weber, Brom (Box 140, Folder 23)
    - Webster, Harvey Curtis (Box 140, Folder 24)
    - We, Weeks, Robert Lewis Wei, Wang Weigel, Henrietta Weil, James L. Weiler, Kaywynne Weinheber, Joseph Weinreich, Uriel (Box 140, Folder 25)
    - We, Weinstein, Arnold Weisenthal, Morris Weismiller, Edward (Box 140, Folder 26)
    - Weiss, Neil SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 140, Folder 27)
    - Weiss, Neil (Box 140, Folder 28)
    - Weiss, Sanford (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Weiss, Ted SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Weiss, Ted (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Weiss, Ted (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - We-Wh, Weisstein, Allyn Weisstein, Ulrich Wells, Marie West, J. Susan D. West, John Foster West, Paul West, Ray Weston, Mildred Wevill, David Whatley, Mary Wharton, Gordon (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Wheelock, John Hall (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Wh, Whitbread, Thomas B. White, C. Clark White, E. W. White, Joan White, Lynn Whiteaker, Stafford Whitecomb, Donald (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Whitman, Ruth (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Whittemore, Reed SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Whittemore, Reed SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Whittemore, Reed SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 141, Folder 11)